⊸GEORGE KINYUA —

IT SPECIALIST/REPAIR U.S MARINES

CONTACT

PHONE: 404-437-9101

EMAIL: Georgewes38@gmail.com

ADDRESS: P.O Box 1589 Marietta, Ga 30061

PROFILE

Dedicated IT specialist with 5+ years of experience. Previous positions involved network management and database administration. A Team player, having led several university projects. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of device repair, imaging, 3D Engineering and computer integrated manufacturing skills to successfully fill the level of a repair technician role at your company. Frequently praised as focused by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

SKILLS AND CERTIFICATIONS

- Microsoft Office and Spreadsheets
- Analytical and critical thinker
- Operating Systems- Windows , IOS, Android, Chrome, Linux
- Ticketing systems ServiceNow, Zendesk, Spiceworks, Jit bit
- Dell/Lenovo/HP/Lexmark Certifications
- IT security best practices
- Network and system upgrades
- MATLAB, LTspice, CAD, Pspice software

EDUCATION

WOODSTOCK HIGH SCHOOL - Woodstock, GA

- High School Diploma (June 2019) GPA (3.5)
- Awards & Honors (Student of the Month(s) and Boy scout of the year)

KENNESAW STATE UNIVERSITY - Kennesaw, GA

- Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering, Minor in Information Technology – GPA (3.2)
- Currently in Junior Year (Expected graduation Dec 2024)
- Awards & Honors (National Science Fair 2nd position and , Volunteer Service Award)
- Young Professional Engineer Award

EXPERIENCE

IT SPECIALIST/ BREAK-FIX TECHNICIAN - PROLOGIC ITS (Acworth, GA)

April 2022 - Current

- Troubleshoot, install, or resolve software/hardware issues using departmental procedures, following design or installation specifications.
- Imaging, quality checking, PC repairs, inventory tracking, and preparing new and repurposed assets for deployment to end clients.
- Adhered to established ESD guidelines, repair procedures, and associated safety standards.
- Diagnose most equipment problems using appropriate tools, test equipment, and documentation.

COMPUTER REPAIR TECHNICIAN - STAYMOBILE LLC (Kennesaw, GA)

April 2021 - April 2022

- Produced test procedures for different types of products, installed and configured operating system software and upgrades.
- > Troubleshooted software, hardware, network issues & peripherals.
- Diagnosed and replaced damaged components.
- Executed service delivery by performing: PC break-fix; MAC break-fix, Desk Side support and installs.

ELECTRICAL ASSEMBLY TECHNICIAN – ROYTEC INDUSTRIES (Canton, GA)

Jan 2020 - Apr 2021

- Read and interpreted schematic drawings, diagrams, blueprints, specifications, work orders, and reports to determine materials requirements and assembly instructions.
- Assembled electrical or electronic systems and support structures; and installed components, units, subassemblies, wiring, and assembly casings, using rivets, bolts, soldering and micro-welding equipment.
- Connected wiring to accessories such us relays, circuit breakers, plugs, switches and installed accessory assemblies in electrical and electronic units using hand tools and soldering guns.

APPLICATIONS ENGINEER/ PC TECHNICIAN SUPPORT - ENDEAVOR 3D (Hiram, GA)

Aug 2018 - Dec 2019

- > Designed, integrated, and improved 3D Printing systems or related processes.
- Determined root causes of failures or recommended changes in designs, tolerances, or processing methods, using statistical procedures.
- > Analyze systems and processes, maintaining workstations and networks.
- Installs, repairs, and maintains hardware, software updates, and peripherals and interfacing to network and/or main computer systems.
- Performance break-fix and/or troubleshooting on various Sun/Oracle, IBM, Dell/EMC, HP, NetApp and Cisco/Brocade Enterprise servers, switches and storage at local data center.